# **ROY CHUA YUEN ZHENG**

**Mobile Number** (+65) 97860507

**Email**roystal@gmail.com

**Address**Singapore 669627

**LinkedIn** www.linkedin.com/in/roy-chuayz

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate and hardworking undergraduate with an interest in problem-solving and innovating technical solutions to help realise businesses' objectives. Highly adaptable and dependable with numerous experiences and knowledge in managing and developing IT solutions.

In the pursuit of opportunities to further develop love for innovation and critical thinking.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### National University of Singapore

Bachelor of Computing, Information Systems (Hons)

#### Matriculated in 08/2020 Expected in 05/2024

- Vice President of NUS Students' Computing Club
- External Liaison Executive of NUS Entrepreneurship Society
- Project Director of Computing Freshmen Orientation Week 2021
- Publicity Director of NUS Volleyball Club
- N-House AY21/22

## **SKILLS**

- Java (JPA / EJB)
- Flutter (Dart)
- UX Design & Interactive Design Thinking
- Technology integration
- Entrepreneurship expertise
- Critical thinking
- Flexible & Adaptable
- IT Management
- Project Management
- Model-based system engineering
- Dashboard development
- Software Development

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Technology Consultant Intern**

Ernst & Young | June 2021 - Aug 2021

- Was involved in 2 SAP projects for a Multinational TYO Listed Company
- Liaised with external developers as well as partners to ensure deadlines of the different product stages are met
- Involved in role design and development using SAP MDG and Integrated single sign-on authentication via SAP IAS for clients
- Led the drafting of compliance documents (CSV)
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Drafted pitch decks for SAP IAS Implementation to potential clients

## **Programmer Analyst Intern**

NTUC Enterprise | Feb 2020 - July 2020

- Directed 2 out of 4 projects during my Internship
- Consulted stakeholders from the Strategy and Finance Team to to establish system designs and ensure product and project success
- Designed and implemented a KPI-tracking system across the organisation coupled with a connected C-Suite level KPI Dashboard
- Directed the consolidation and creation of Finance Data into Custom Dashboards for the Leadership Team
- Work with REST APIs to connect Live Data to Google Data Studio Dashboards
- Involved in web development of Company-wide Intranet
- Familiarised with UI Path and Robotic Process Automation (RPA)
  Development.

## **Operations Intern**

Propseller | Dec 2019 - Feb 2020

- Liaise with both Inside Sales and Real Estate Agents to ensure business success
- Build and manage company's cloud database -
- Reorganize and reformulate data fields in Airtable
- Conduct research and prepare sales materials for the outside sales team
- Collect property information and ensure data accuracy in system
- Boosted customer experiences by delivering superior customer service, issue resolution and merchandising.